investni.com 2015-12-07

# Privacy

###  Personal information held by us.

* * *

This privacy notice tells you what to expect when Invest NI collects personal information. It applies to information we collect about:

  * Visitors to our website.
  * People who use our services including Invest NI customers, participants in our programmes or services and attendees at events we organise. It also includes those who use the Business Information Centre.

We review our privacy notice regularly and will place any updates on this page. This privacy policy applies only to Invest Northern Ireland and its website. We are not responsible for the privacy practices within any other websites that you may link to from this site.

**Visitors to our website**  
When someone visits our website we collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behaviour patterns. We do this to find out things like the number of visitors to the various parts of Invest NI’s website. We collect this information in a way which does not identify anyone.

The tool we use to analyse visitor patterns uses 'cookies', which are text files placed on your computer to collect information. You can decide if you want to accept or reject cookies by changing the settings on your browser.

We will not associate any data gathered from this site with any personally identifying information from any source. If we do want to collect personally identifiable information through our web site, we will make it clear when we collect it and will explain what we intend to do with it.

**People who use Invest NI services**  
We need to hold the details of the people who have requested access to our programmes and services in order to provide them with the necessary advice or support. The data that we keep on record may include your name, company name, contact details, financial information and employment details. Please do not provide us with information if you do not want it stored.

**Security of your personal information**  
Invest NI carefully protects your data from loss, misuse, unauthorised access, disclosure or alteration in line with information governance policies as detailed in our [Information Security Handbook](https://secure.investni.com/static/library/invest-ni/documents/information-governance-information-security-handbook.pdf "Download our Information Security Handbook PDF \(Opens in New Window\)"). Internally, data is stored in password-controlled servers with restricted access. Information will be destroyed in line with the retention schedule within our [Records Management Policy](https://secure.investni.com/static/library/invest-ni/documents/records-management-policy-invest-ni-v1-6-october-2011-km.pdf "Download our Records Management Policy PDF \(Opens in New Window\)").

**Disclosure of personal information**  
To deliver a service we may need to share your information with the Department of Enterprise, Trade and Investment (DETI), other agencies involved in economic development, organisations that deliver our programmes, and the European Commission. We will never pass on information other than for the purpose for which it was provided to us.

When you provide personal information to us, you understand and agree that:

  * This may involve the information being used by Invest NI and DETI for direct marketing and other economic development related activities.
  * Invest NI, DETI or another public agency providing economic development activities may contact you directly in the future to offer services related to the one for which you provided your details to Invest NI.
  * It may involve the transfer of data outside the European Economic Area to our overseas offices.
  * Invest NI may send you marketing information by email.

As required by law, we may disclose information to government bodies and law enforcement agencies for their enforcement purposes.

Invest NI will not sell your personal information.

**Opt-out to disclosure of personal information**  
If you do not want your details to be used in any of the ways described above, please tell us. Please note that it may not be possible to provide some Invest NI services if you do not allow us to disclose information provided to us.

You can opt out at any time from receiving marketing material by emailing enquiry@investni.com

**Access to personal information**  
You can find out if we hold any personal information about you by making a 'subject access request' under the Data Protection Act 1998. If we do hold information about you we will:

  * Give you a description of it.
  * Tell you why we are holding it.
  * Tell you who it could be disclosed to.
  * Let you have a copy of the information in an intelligible form.

**Accuracy of personal information**  
While we try to keep our data current, we request that you inform us of any changes in your personal information so that we may keep our records up to date.

**Freedom of Information**  
In releasing information under the Freedom of Information Act 2000 we will strive to ensure that we will not conflict with our duties as a data controller under the Data Protection Act 1998.

**Complaints or queries**  
If you think that our collection or use of information is unfair, misleading or inappropriate please contact us through our complaint page or in writing; Complaints & Feedback, Invest Northern Ireland, Bedford Square, Belfast, BT2 7ES. 

If you require a copy of this notice in an alternative format (including Braille, disk, audio cassette or in minority languages to meet the needs of those who are not fluent in English), then please contact the Equality Team on 028 9069 8273; Text phone 028 9069 8585 or email equality@investni.com.

* * *

### Please fill in your details below
